Hello, welcome all of you to Stock Fatafat
and I am Kavita Thapliyal with you.
[Music] In this show, we bring
you all the news related to market action in a quick manner.
In this show,
you are given the best trading ideas for the last 2 hours.  Apart from this,
you are also told about the profit options for earning from investment options.  But let's start
with the big things of the market where
Bank Nifty slipped below 2400 by about 250 points from the day's high [Music] and
here it slipped by about 800 points [Music]
near 56000. Except Metal IT, most of the
sector indices are seen trading in the red mark.
HDB [MUSIC] Financials surges 8% on strong quarterly results
Networks appears to be operating at the moment, losing over 4% on weak quarterly results.
But let's see,
market experts have also joined us here.
[Music] Amol Athavale of Kotak Securities
Amol Hi welcome to Afternoon
and the market appears to be giving up its day's gains.
How do
you see this U-turn in the market?
Yes, Namaste and good afternoon.  It seems like more of a routine
correction.  There was a temporary
overbought condition.  There had already been a descent
rally and 24,500
is a zone which has been considered a crucial resistance
zone previously as well.  So that's where
a correction is triggered.  The way the
setup is and the way the intraday
correction has happened today, I think it may
continue for another day.  On the downside,
if I look at the supports, then
these two support zones 24,000 and 23,900 will be
very important.  This setup will continue as long as it is on top of him.
Ah but a slight
extension of correction can be seen in intraday.
Bank Nifty,
absolutely.  If we look at Bank Nifty even for just one minute, then
today we have definitely seen pressure at the upper level.
56,800 was the resistance taken around the same level yesterday as well.
Even today,
resistance has been taken around the same.  So in the short term,
56,800 will remain an important resistance
point.  The correction is more
because Bank Nifty has still maintained a higher bottom formation.
5500 and
5475 will be two important promising support
zones and if there is a reversal then there will be
more focus on private banks.
All right.  Your trading calls today if you would
like.   Yes of course.  I would like to
go with two stock picks.
Firstly, I would like to go with Eternal.
Is around 248.  I am
looking from a positional point of view.  Targets up to 260 are
coming out.  His stop loss will
be Rs 243.  Consistently the
stock has maintained a higher bottom formation.
Positive setup.  If there is a
change in market sentiment, then there will
definitely be focus on Eternal stock.  The second one
is a contrabass.  Looking for a pullback.
That is CPL is around 1230.   The
continuation of the technical bounce back can be
seen in the coming days.   The
Broader setup is still bad, though.  But the
chances of a sharp bounce back are
visible in SPLA.  On the higher side the
target will be 1280.  Its stop loss will be Rs
1210.
All right.  So here in the returns you have
given a target of 260 and you have recommended a stop loss of 253
and these are your today's
trading calls which you are recommending.
We will move ahead and
move towards news maker stocks in a stock specific conversation.  Let's
talk about Gayle.  There is an
agreement with Tusco here.  The company is seen signing agreements
for 16 projects totaling approximately 600 MW in Uttar Pradesh.  At
the moment, we see an upmove of 1% recorded.
An upmove of almost 3% in the last five trading sessions but
a dip in between where we
saw levels up to 150 but after that an upmove is being
maintained.  But since it is in range,
how are you looking at the last five trading sessions
?
Yes, you are absolutely right.  It is within the range and
chances of continuation of the same range can be
seen in the short term.  On the
higher side, there will be a resistance zone
for GAIL at 163-165 and on the
downside, if I look at 150, where a
higher bottom formation was formed, it will be an immediate
support zone.  The range is a bit big
150 165 but considering the volatility and the
pattern in the short term,
I think the stock can be seen trading within this range.
Okay let's talk about a Signature Global.
He has signed an agreement with Italian company TNO Lamborghini.  And the agreement that has been made is
regarding the development of a residential project in Gurugram.  At present it is
quite flat but the price of 8185 is visible in the red mark.
How are you looking?
After the bounce back, a dull momentum has been seen.
Especially since the last three days.
However, the setup is still on the positive side.
825 or 820 will be such a level, if it is
cleared then I think the chances of a fresh
uptrend rally coming from here are quite
bright.  If one is looking from a positional point of view
then immediate support will be
around 780 775 positionally.  And
if the stock clears 825, then the bullish
momentum and chances of growth are quite bright
on the higher side.  The first resistance will be
850-860 and the second resistance will be 875.
Okay Alumbic Pharma is our next news maker
stock and the
injection has been approved here.
This medicine is used in the treatment of psoriasis and cancer.
Currently up about 2.5% in today's trade.
In the last 6 months, the prices have
started breaking below 1000 here.
We are continuously seeing that it is breaking down.
Ah, how are you seeing
this trend?
Alumbic Pharma you asked right?   Yes yes,
just
watch it in APL for a minute, one bounce back was
quite sharp.  A support was formed around 660.
If I look before that, a
long correction was seen.  But
after that, the bounce back that has come in the stock has
maintained the uptrend in it,
so it is a bounce back only but it can continue
till 780 and its immediate support is
720, as long as it is above 720, this pullback
formation can be seen
continuing somewhere or the other in the short term as well
in the coming days.
Ok Amaro lets talk about infra enginers.
From March till now, they have received orders worth approximately Rs 2240 crore.
Ah,
they have received this order for waste water renewable energy system.
Currently, an upmove of 1%
is recorded.  How do you view the stock in the short term
?
My one minute
ji is not in your coverage.   OK, I
cannot comment.  Not in coverage.
Ok.  Is GAV Infra in your coverage?
No, sorry.
Ok.  Let's move on.  Let's talk about Tejas network.
Where if
we look at the numbers, the consolidated income figure has
come to around Rs 1906 crore and has come down to around Rs 333
crore.  And we are seeing that
year on year numbers here are
showing weakness.  The stock is also
falling.  What are the treasury charts saying going forward
?
Stuck in a range.  The bounce back was quite
sharp.  After that there was a dull momentum.
Today a correction of up to 4.5% was seen.
On the higher side, the stock can
definitely bounce back to around 460.  But a big
move is possible only if the stock starts trading above 460, then the
chances of a positional setup change are
visible on the charts.  On the lower
side if I look then 400 410 has been the
immediate support zone.  In case, if the
range breaks downwards and the
stock is seen trading below 400, then an
extension of the correction may also be
seen.  We OK ICICI Lbar
Q4 results profit increased from Rs 510 crore to Rs 54
crore.  Final dividend of ₹ per share has
also been announced.  Net
premium income has increased from approximately Rs 5225 crore to Rs 5790
crore.  The combined ratio here has
come down from 104% to around 101%.
Quarter-end stock is up almost 1.5%.
How are you looking?   There
is positive momentum.  If momentum is to be chased
then I think 8825 will be a
reference point for traders.
However, there is a consistent
resistance zone at the higher level at 1950.  But
if we look at the kind of bounce back that has happened this week specifically, then there has been a bounce back of around 6%.  A
very sharp bounce backup has been
seen.  The way the setup is
on the intraday charts, I think
this momentum will definitely continue and on the higher
side, 1950 will be the resistance.
Allright talks about Comcor and
they have got an order of Rs 175 crore with Bitw & Company.
They seem to be getting this order for wagon supply.
Currently there is an
upmove of almost 8% technically on the charts.
What should be done now at these levels?   You
can hold or those who already have it
can trail it with a stop loss of Rs 485
as the setup looks quite promising.  The
bounce back was also quite sharp.   The
low was around 420.  So after that the
stock has consistently maintained an up trend.  It is the
short term average.
Comfortable trading has been seen happening on this also.
On the higher side, if this
momentum continues, the immediate
resistance zone for the stock will be at
515 and the second resistance zone will be at
525.
HDFC AMC numbers are coming.  Once this is done,
pull it on the screen.  Consolidated
profits here appear to be declining slightly.
But if we
talk about consolidated income, then
it seems to be increasing from Rs 901 crore to Rs 1050 crore.
Profit is seen
declining from ₹639 crore to ₹623 crore.  The
company has also announced a final dividend of ₹54 per share.
A So these are the first set of numbers that we see
coming.  HDFC AMC is seeing
further revenue growth but we are seeing pressure on profits.
On the overall technical front,
do you like this stock in this space
and what is your strategy in the short term
?
In the short term, there will be a wait and watch
approach.  Purely if I look at the short term then
because 2750 2800 was
a resistance zone positionally as well on
daily and weekly charts and whenever this
stock triggers a correction around that level, then if the
correction goes quite deep then there
is a big range and the kind of momentum that has happened,
it has already made a very promising rally from the bottom.
Momentum indicators
are indicating that this is a temporary overbought condition
and today we have also seen pressure at the upper levels.   There
is selling pressure in the market also.  So there will be a
bit of a wait and watch approach.
If this correction happens then I think
this correction can continue till 2550.
Although this is a limited correction, but at present,
if I am looking at any move for the short term, then it should be a
wait and watch approach.
This tech is currently running on HDFC AMC
and these results are coming on your screen.
Welcome back. You are watching Stock Fatafat and
we are focusing on news maker stocks.
Amol Athawale is our guest today who is
giving you guidance.  HDB
Financial Amol, our next stock in
concern, has reported strong results in Q4.  Asset
quality has improved.  Net
NPA has come down from 1.25% to around 1% now.
This number is on quarter on quarter basis.  Would you have
any recommendations in your coverage
?   There is
no recommendation, my view on it
is neutral but the kind of bounce
back that has been seen, it is
going on around 694, I guess yes, it is going on around 694, the
kind of bounce back that has been seen this week, a
sharp bounce back of 11%,
it seems that the uptick may continue further,
if I look at the levels, then 680 will be the immediate support
zone, the second one will be around 670, on the
higher side, the immediate resistance zone in this stock will be
740 and 750.
Allright RTL Our next stock in concern is
related to IT solution, they have got an order of Rs 100 crore.  There has been a
continuous discussion about RT.
Will you tell me what to do now?
Yes, it has been a very promising rally.  Especially the
momentum yesterday was quite sharp.
After that, today some profit booking was
definitely seen at the higher level.  But the
way the overall fashion is, I think
buy on dips, sell on rallies would be the
ideal strategy for RT, especially for the short
term.  If we talk about supports, then 320 is a little
deep, these two support zones 320 and 325 are
emerging.  On the higher
side, the immediate resistance zone today will be
around the day's high of 355 and 360.
If the stock trades below 320, the
setup may change.  Otherwise, there are chances of the buy on
deep sell on rallies setup continuing
in the short term.
Brigade Enterprises Next News Maker
Stock The company has signed an agreement for 8.63 acres of land in Bengaluru.
Very flat at the moment but
keep your distance at these levels.
Yes, we can wait.  The reason behind that is that the
stock already has a
lower top formation on the daily and weekly charts.  Whenever the bounce
back has been rested or the selling pressure has increased at
higher levels, the correction has been quite sharp.  The
stock has also taken time.  There will be a bit of a
wait and watch approach.
A profit booking is being seen today after a recent rally.  If we
talk about supports, there
is definitely support around 700.  But wait
and watch approach will remain.
All right.   Let's move
ahead and GAP Infra you said is
not on your coverage.  Right?
Yes, there is no coverage pay.
Ok.  Ides come to life.
Oekology plant in Ahmedabad has received EIR.
After the pre-approval inspection, they have received the
establishment inspection report from USFDS.
How do you see this
development and its impact technically
?   The
technical setup is good.  After a reversal, the
stock has sustained at higher levels.
However, 920-930 was a very crucial
resistance zone.
Profit booking was seen there repeatedly.  Sharp
corrections were seen.  But still, in the current
setup,
trading is seen happening comfortably above 920.
This will be the reference point.  If someone is
chasing momentum, then 920 is
above it, then this setup will remain.  960
is the first resistance zone.  After that, I
think there are chances of the bullish momentum
continuing somewhere till 980
in the short term.   Let's
talk about A Most of Technologies
and here for the acquisition it will issue 51 lakh
shares and the acquisition will be in 73% stake.  Would
an upward move of 1/4% be
in your coverage?
Running around 192.  Right?
Running around 192.  Correct is up 4%.
This has bounced back.  My view
is neutral.  His graph is not that available.
But attention will definitely be paid to the 200 day simple moving average
which is coming
around 200.  The level of 200 will be an
important resistance zone.  Although it
is volatile.  Movements are taking place in the stock on both sides.
On the downside, the support
will be at 180 and on the higher side, the resistance
zone will be at ₹200.
All right.  It's time for our special
segment, Profit Options.
[Music]
Ratesh Kol, our guest today,
will explain strategy.  Ratansh Aayi Afternoon where are you
giving advice today?
Or Hi Kavita Savita, Namaskar, absolutely,
look at the market, there has definitely been
profit booking from the higher part, but I feel that the
market will settle back somewhere around ₹2450, from
this a
good breakout will be seen in PFC and RC, a good
formation is being formed in PFC, here it is advisable to take a call strike of ₹470, by
placing a stop loss of ₹3 at around ₹6, the target which can be made is
₹11, so the risk reward ratio
is in favor, the loss which can be made is ₹3250,
profit can be ₹6500,
all right, this strategy comes and your
call today is in PFC.  Thank you Ratash and Amol,
thank you very much too.  You gave me time,
explained the strategy and participated in the show with the audience today.  That's all for
stock fast.  Please allow me also.  A
short break, after that we will
bring Copyd Connection.  Stay tuned, greetings.